Guide to the Charles W. Duncan, Jr. business papers, 1958-2013 MS 583
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V. Addendum, 176185
  - Sub-Series II. Memoir, 176187
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177921 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 13: Ranch, 177922 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 2-4, 177923 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Draft Chapters 1-7, 177924 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Draft Chapters 8-14, 177925 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 2-7, 177926 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Annotated Draft chapters 8-12, 177927 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 2: Early Years; Chapter 3: Duncan Coffee, 177928 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Annotated Draft Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177929 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapter 6: Washington, Defense Dept., 177930 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Revision Pages, 177931 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-7, 177932 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177933 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapters 1-7, 177934 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapters 8-14, 177935 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 1-7, 177936 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177937 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177938 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177939 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177940 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Annotated Draft: Chapters 8-14, 177941 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Annotated Draft: Ttile Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177942 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177943 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapter 10: Education, Rice University, 177944 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Annotated Draft: Chapter 10, 177945 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Draft and Handwritten Notes, Chapter 10: Education, 177946 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C. Chapters 1-7, 177947 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177948 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Questions and Chapter Notes, 177949 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177950 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177951 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177952 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapters 8-14, 177953 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Research and Notes, Department of Energy, 2012, 177954 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Letter to Charles and Anne from Chris July 18, 2012, 177955 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Remaining Questions, 177956 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Draft with some annotation: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177957 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Draft with some annotation Chapters 8-13, 177958 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Annotated Draft: T.O.C. Chapters 1-7, 177961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177962 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C., Chapters 1-7, 177964 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Annotated Draft Chapters 8-14, 177965 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Annotated Draft: Title Page, T.O.C. Chapters 1-7, 177968 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Annotated Draft: Chapters 8-14, 177970 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Final Draft Chapters 1-7, 177972 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Final Draft Chapters 8-13, 177974 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Flash Drive containing Drafts, 177976 (Box 32, Envelope 16)
  - Sub-series III. Miscellaneous, 177087
    - Policy Consensus Report: U.S. Energy Policy, 1992; 177089 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Report: Texas National Research Laboratory Commission and the Superconducting Super Collider (2 folders), November 12, 2002; 177088 (Box 32, Folder 18-19)